Host:
```javascript
data:text/html,<script>const script = document.createElement('script'); script.src = 'https://cs6413110.github.io/kahoot/host.js'; document.head.appendChild(script);</script>
```

Join:
```javascript
data:text/html,<script>const script = document.createElement('script'); script.src = 'https://cs6413110.github.io/kahoot/join.js'; document.head.appendChild(script);</script>
```
```javascript
[{"question": "What is the python division operator?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["/", "/=", "%", "%="]}, {"question": "What are python's conditional keywords?", "correct": "3", "answers": ["if, then, else", "if, and, or", "if, and, or, else", "if, else, elif"]}, {"question": "What is a Boolean in python?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["A true or false value", "A operator", "A library", "A key-value data structure"]}, {"question": "What is a string in python?", "correct": "1", "answers": ["A single character", "A data type for handling text", "A list of different data types", "A key-value data structure"]}, {"question": "What function prints to the console?", "correct": "2", "answers": ["log", "write", "print", "text"]}, {"question": "What function asks for user input?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["input", "request", "prompt", "require"]}, {"question": "What library have we used for random numbers?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["random", "math", "rand", "python"]}, {"question": "What is an argument?", "correct": "1", "answers": ["A data structure", "Values you pass to a function", "A function return type", "A type of function"]}, {"question": "What does the \"return\" keyword do?", "correct": "1", "answers": ["Stop execution of a function", "Stop execution and return a value", "Return a value", "Save the function to be called for later"]}, {"question": "What is the difference between a float and an int?", "correct": "2", "answers": ["Floats are for big numbers", "Floats are for negative numbers", "Floats are for decimals", "Floats are for fractions"]}, {"question": "What data type would be best for storing someone's age?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["integer", "string", "float", "boolean"]}, {"question": "What data type would be best for storing average test score?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["float", "boolean", "string", "array"]}, {"question": "What is the exponent operator?", "correct": "2", "answers": ["*=", "*", "**", "**="]}, {"question": "What is the increment operator?", "correct": "3", "answers": ["+", "-", "=", "+="]}, {"question": "What is the multiplication operator?", "correct": "3", "answers": ["x", "times", "mul", "*"]}, {"question": "What is the keyword for defining a function?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["def", "function", "func", "exe"]}, {"question": "What is the assignment operator?", "correct": "3", "answers": ["set", "equals", "assign", "="]}, {"question": "What is the error: print(\"Hello World!)", "correct": "2", "answers": ["Undefined function", "Invalid token", "Missing quotation mark", "No return value"]}, {"question": "What function correctly returns the sum of a and b?", "correct": "2", "answers": ["def m(): return a+b", "def m(a, b): do a+b", "def m(a, b): return a+b", "def m(a, b) a+b"]}, {"question": "What library does techsmart have for ui?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["tsapp", "gui", "python", "window"]}, {"question": "What would you use an array for?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["Storing a list of values", "Storing a long value", "Storing something for a short amount of time", "Storing variables"]}, {"question": "What would you use a dict for?", "correct": "1", "answers": ["Storing multiple values", "Storing key-value pairs", "Encrypting algorithms", "Performance"]}, {"question": "What is wrong with this code: prin(\"Hello World!\")", "correct": "0", "answers": ["Spelling mistake", "Invalid string", "Missing quotation mark", "No parenthesis"]}, {"question": "What function typecasts to a string?", "correct": "2", "answers": ["string", "toString", "str", "txt"]}, {"question": "How do you declare an array?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["[]", "Array", "arr", "num"]}, {"question": "What is a valid variable name?", "correct": "2", "answers": ["float", "var/iable", "_", "8th_test"]}, {"question": "What is a function?", "correct": "0", "answers": ["A defined block of code to be run later", "A data type", "Multiple arguments", "A return value"]}]
```
